Lesson one is about getting prepared for
the PMP exam.
And so these are just some of the learning
objectives.
So first of all, we want to know who is
actually eligible to take the PNP exam.
So we'll cover that.
We'll also learn about how to complete the
PMP application.
So what's the actual application process?
We'll talk about that.
Also, we'll talk about the format of the
PNP exam.
What to expect on exam day?
What kind of questions you're going to get
in the test?
sense, what kind of format of questions.
So we'll be, we'll be talking about the
actual exam itself.
And then also some basic tips and tricks.
There's a lot of curveballs that PMI might
throw at you on the exam.
It's not enough to know the materials.
But there's also a lot of exam technique
that you need to learn.
Right.
You need to learn to pick out key words
and key phrases.
And, you know, you need to be able to
navigate through a PMP exam question.
There's a lot of ambiguities in the PNP
exam question, right?
You need to be able to navigate through
all of these ambiguous situations, right?
So we'll be giving you some tips and
tricks, right, in this section as well.
What kind of things to look out for on an
exam question?